All right, okay. So we can make this very interactive. So as I go along with like building
some components and talking to Cloud Code to build things for us, you can ask questions
at any time.
So Issam, I just have one question right there for you. So the other day, Pavel mentioned
that you can use Codex, which is equally as good.
Yeah.
So would you be giving the instructions, are the same instructions that are applicable
for Codex as well?
So I haven't used Codex, but since Pavel mentioned that they're equivalent, you could potentially
just use the same prompts.
Okay.
That's the one we'd be using for Cloud Code.
Got it.
Okay.
Yeah.
So today we'll be building something called the MoneyClaw, which is about...
looking at your finances, like looking at your emails related to the amount of money you
have received or the amount of money you have given.
And then it analyzes that and it gives you a nice summary of these kinds of transactions,
and then send them to your Telegram and also generate a dashboard for that.
So this is what I'm going to be building.
So one of the tasks that we had was implementing that flowchart.
So this is the thing we're going to start with.
So we're going to implement a flowchart.
Let's me...
Excalibur is very nice for that.
Okay.
So let's create that flowchart.
So first, let's call this MoneyClaw.
And let me put some money in a second.
There you go, MoneyClaw.
And just better with me.
And this is for this MoneyClaw is like a Personal Assistant for Optimizing Spendings.
So this is the title.
And now we're going to put some flowchart with nodes and edges.
So remember when we talked about the flowchart includes the agent itself, like the AI model,
it also includes the data connectors and the tools.
So data connector could be Gmail.
And let's say this is where we gather all the transactions.
And then we can have, let's say, Google Calendar, which let's say contains some meetings.
Maybe based on the meetings, I mean, you don't have to really include that here.
But like, maybe the meetings can help you.
Let's say you're trying to optimize spendings or like you optimize your money.
Some meetings might be useful.
Some meetings might be not.
Let's say you're meeting with investors.
So you have to prioritize those first, for example.
So this is where the Google Calendar meetings can help with optimizing your spendings.
And then we can also have Notion.
So these are the data connectors.
Okay, Notion.
And let's say Notion has some of your high-level goals.
So a high-level goal is like how much you want to spend per month and what's your goal in like one year, two years, or three years.
So you can use that to guide your AI agent to give you the best next action items or what you need to prioritize so that you optimize your spending.
So it's just like a high-level goals could be your yearly goals, your monthly goals, and your daily and your weekly goals, for example.
So these are the data connectors.
And then we're going to add an AI agent.
And the service that we use for our AI agent is going to be OpenRouter plus LineGraph.
LineGraph is a nice Python library that allows you to implement good AI agents that are similar to cloud code.
So this is the AI agent that works in your app.
So you use cloud code, for example, to write your app.
But within the app itself, you can have an AI agent that does things for you, like summarize your transactions and so on.
So the data connectors, let's color code them as yellow.
And the AI agent is color coded as blue.
And then let's add some tools.
So a tool could be the web search.
So let's say, when you look at your Gmail and you look at your transactions,
some of the transactions could be like subscriptions you have to different services like Grave, Netflix, and so on.
So the web search can be used to see if there's any alternatives.
So let's say you're paying a lot for Netflix, let's say.
So the web search can find alternatives to Netflix based on your interest in terms of movies.
So maybe you don't need to subscribe to Netflix and you just need to,
you can just subscribe to, let's say, Amazon Prime.
Or to Grave, based on your interest in the type of movie.
So it might be able to help you reduce the amount of subscriptions that you have.
And now a lot of us have a lot of different subscriptions.
But that brings a question to me, Issam.
So doing the web search, right?
So this is an agent who, like, is that a second agent?
No, right?
It's only one agent who can perform this web search.
Exactly.
Yeah, yes, exactly.
Okay.
So you have one AI agent and it's orchestrating all these, like, tools and data connectors.
So when it color coded as red, that means it's a tool, like a service.
It's like web search.
Okay.
Another, yeah, exactly.
So another tool could be send to Telegram.
Oops.
Send to Telegram.
And this could be used for summarization.
And then you can have another tool, which is create report on Notion, which could have like,
which could summarize all your spendings.
Let me just make them all the same size.
And then you can have another tool, which is about generating a dashboard.
So it's always, it's always nice to have like a dashboard that shows all your spendings,
especially like tax season, right?
And when it comes to tax season, it's always a good opportunity to see all your expenses and all your
income to see how you have spent your money over the last year, for example.
So it's always nice to have like a dashboard of where you've been spending your money.
Okay.
So now let's put some connectors.
By connectors, I mean like how things interact with each other.
So you have these.
So you have Google Calendar goes to the agents.
You have Notion that goes to the agent as well.
And then you have this agent that does.
So from the AI agent, it goes to the tools themselves, because this is what it's using.
And the data connectors go to the agent itself.
So the AI agent here goes to this, sending to telegram.
Let me just finish this quickly.
There you go.
All right.
So this is our figure.
And something cool to put is to put a legend.
So let's put this this way.
And we can.
Legend is always nice to put in a figure to understand like what each node represents.
So I'm just building a legend here.
This one here.
If there's any confusion or anything.
Yeah.
What is the legend?
So this is.
So this box is the legend.
So it specifies what each node represents based on the color.
Okay.
So yellow here is data connectors.
Let's make them medium.
And then blue here means LLMs.
You can have multiple LMs.
It doesn't have to be one only.
And then the.
Yeah.
Go ahead, Edward.
Basically, I have a question about connectors and tools and the difference between connectors
and tools in this case, because, you know, in my, according to my personal feeling,
connectors are doing almost the same as tools should do.
Yeah.
They're very similar.
I mean, everything can be considered as a tool or everything can be considered as a component.
The only distinguishing factor here is like, where do you get your data from?
And then the tools here is like the things that the agent interacts with to perform an action.
So the tool here is like the agent will use the web search to find things or sense
to telegram or create a report.
Yeah.
Because basically, telegram by itself should be a connector, in my opinion.
But, you know, it's just a difference in definitions and maybe not so important details.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
I mean, they can all be called tools, like you said.
But if you go like more specific, the main difference here is that the tools is like the
thing that the agent performs and the data connectors is like the data sources.
You can even call it data sources instead of data connectors.
So you can call them data sources.
Yeah.
Or call tools tasks or jobs that the agent does?
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, yeah.
Or a service.
This tool is a bit confusing.
I'm also like when I think of tools, I think of either LLM or like an actual tool.
LLM could be a tool as well.
Yeah.
So what?
Yeah, go ahead.
No, no.
It's all semantics.
It's just the words.
Isam, is it that you are talking, you're saying this as tool because Telegram itself
as a tool, Notion as a tool, and Web App as a tool, and then the action itself is sending it,
you know, to Telegram.
Like that is the action that is being performed by the agent.
Exactly.
I mean, it could be cool.
So another semantics tools could be also called like services.
So it's connecting to these services to generate dashboard reports.
So a tool could also be an LLM, right?
But the LLM here, what I mean by LLMs here, means like the brain.
It's like, this is the brain or the orchestrator.
The one that, so it's got the decision making, basically.
Exactly.
So it grabs the things from the data sources or the data connections.
Maybe data source is even better word.
I mean, these are all, you know, so there's no specific standard.
So this could be called data sources.
This is the brain.
And these tools are like the services where the agent like sends things to.
Does that make sense?
Sorry, I'm a bit confused about the AI agent part.
Doesn't more have to go in for this to be an agent?
Because like the agent is a consolidation of the brain, the skills, the personality
and everything, right?
It's like an integration type thing.
Yeah.
So within the AI agent itself, we can have other things like, for example, memory.
So memory, like the things that keeps track of your, let's say, your personality or like what you've
been doing so far.
So the agent is more than just the LLM.
Yeah.
Maybe an agent is even better than.
Like agent itself is like a better way to describe it.
Right?
Yeah.
So you can call it an agent.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Right.
Except like in this example here, we would be focusing on just like direct LLM invoking,
but an agent is, yeah, it would say like it's a better word here.
But yes, the whole harness around the LLM.
It's not just the LLM.
It's like, it's a brain.
So you remember, like we talked about memory and Saul.
Saul could be the personality of the agent itself.
So all of these are part of the agent, these blue parts.
So you have here, for example.
All right.
So this is our figure.
Does that make sense of like what are we trying to implement?
I have a question here related to Saul.
So what if you don't put a soul, like you don't put a personality,
then what a personality would, does it opt for?
So the most basic personality that these LLMs have is like, you are a helpful AI assistant.
That's pretty much it.
Okay.
Do you want to add some other attributes?
Sorry?
Yeah, attributes.
Exactly.
And what are the other attributes?
Like you are a helpful agent.
But like, you know, when we would be explicitly talking about Saul,
we would mention a lot of creative details, so to say.
But over here in this case, if it is just AI assistant, like,
is there anything else to it or that's about it?
Well, so instead of just your helpful AI assistant, it could be you are
an accountant who understands finance.
So it's like a system prompt to give it a personality.
You're an accountant.
Okay.
Here's an example.
You're an accountant who is focused on optimizing spendings.
And then you can say, make sure the amount of money that you spend is only $500 per month.
Okay, that's maybe not realistic.
$5,000 a month, let's say.
And any time there's more than $5,000, it's a red flag.
Or any time you're not spending that much, you can spend other things.
You can add all those like details, like the goals, the values, the personality, your goals.
So you can imagine all your goals, all your personal goals and
and your view of where you should spend on like your priorities could be put in the soul.
You know, that's the idea.
Got it.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Okay, so this will be our basis of our agent.
We're not going to implement everything, but I'm just going to show you like how to
implement some of them.
So that's like when you work on your own personal assistant,
you'll have an idea on how to implement all the different components and the workflows.
Okay, so first things first, let's go to GitHub and create a repository name.
If you don't know GitHub, so GitHub is just a repository where,
well, GitHub is a platform where you can create projects
and maintain all your code bases.
It's a very nice way to do what we call version control.
Because, you know, like when you interact with cloud,
cloud code and so on, and you make changes to your code,
sometimes things break.
And sometimes you want to revert back to previous versions.
So GitHub is a very nice way to keep track of all the versions that you have.
So let's call this MoneyClaw.
MoneyClaw exists.
Let's make it private.
It's always nice to start as private.
Is this in case?
Because when you have all these data connectors and tools,
you'll be using a lot of API keys.
And there's a big risk of like accidentally pushing API keys into the repository.
So that's why starting with private to make sure that nothing is being,
nothing sensitive is being published first before turning it into a public.
And you only want to turn it into a public if you want other people to collaborate on it,
or if you want to open source your code so that people can use your code.
And then to help the world use like your new software, for example.
So let's create this.
This is I think is in module four.
All right.
So we're going to clone this repo, which is empty, or let's create a readme file.
Commit changes.
Okay, so that's, let me clone this into my computer.
One second.
Let's see the projects.
Hit clone.
There you go.
Now I'm cloning the MoneyClaw, the project.
So I'm going to open that folder.
As you can see, I have a lot of projects here.
There you go.
You see, there's the readme and so on.
Okay, first things first.
Here are some standards that are very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very important.
First one is gitignore.
So gitignore is that when you push to GitHub,
there are certain things that you don't want to push at all.
Like for example, your API keys.
And other files that are not needed to be displayed into GitHub.
It's actually very standard.
So I'm just copy pasting all of this.
But if you ask ChatGPT to give you the .gitignore for any Python project,
this is the type of gitignore.
So all of these folders will be ignored from being pushed to GitHub.
One of the main things that you really need to,
one of the main files that really need to be ignored is .env.
Because .env is where you put all your API keys.
So API keys are the things that allow you to interact with this, say your Gmail,
your maybe Luma, your Notion, and so on.
So these are kept secret.
If you see this grayed out, it means it's not going to be pushed in GitHub.
We will start, this will be filled up with different API keys soon.
Okay, so you have gitignore, you have .env.
One thing that's also very important, which I will upload it into the website,
is having this cloud.md.
So cloud.md, I'm pretty sure Codex has something similar.
So cloud.md will have any instructions
that you want your AI agent to follow every time it generates code.
So I'm going to put some instructions here.
I'm just going to copy paste it, but I'm going to put it online.
In the website.
So these are some instructions.
Like for example, writing code.
Always be concise and use the minimum number of code in libraries.
Make sure to keep things modular.
Don't repeat code.
Use templates.
If you see repeated code, consolidate them.
So all of these are instructions to minimize the number of tokens
and to make sure that your code is structured in a way
that makes it easy for your AI assistants to build on it.
Does that make sense?
Yeah.
And you prompted, where did you get the prompt from to write this?
So this is something I built myself, but you can ask ChatGPT, like,
give me some instructions that I should give to my AI assistant.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Minimize the clutter and to keep things very simple, you know?
Okay.
But you made it, all of these instructions are given by you?
Like you have handwritten them?
Yeah, exactly.
Okay.
Like, because I built so many different apps and so on.
Like, I found that these instructions make it easy for me not to spend, like, hundreds of dollars.
Mm-hmm.
Every time to create an event.
Yeah.
And it creates some project code.
Cool.
Thank you.
Yeah.
So, like, be concise, short answers, no fillers.
There's also this thing which I'm not doing here.
It's called, like, talk like a caveman, which makes it very interesting and reduces the number
of tokens.
So, instead of, like, saying huge paragraphs of what is going on, you can talk like a caveman.
So, a caveman just says, like, one sentence to describe the whole thing.
Like, two, three words to explain the same thing, basically.
Yeah.
Like, bug here, fix this, wrong here, like a caveman.
Yeah, yeah.
But have you said that?
Like, does it work for you?
Like, are you spending less token?
Yeah, I have done it, like, a while ago, but I haven't done it here because I think you have
to be very precise in how you describe the caveman personality, but there's one called
caveman, like, that you can find online on GitHub that you can copy-paste.
Okay.
That exists.
Yeah.
Oh, cool.
This is just to show you, like, different ways you can prompt your AI assistant so that
it becomes as efficient as possible.
Mm, great.
They say with a caveman approach, you can reduce 75% of the number of tokens.
What?
So, instead of 1,000, you only, like, instead of 1,000 tokens,
basically, you're just spending, let's say, 250 tokens.
Right, right.
Okay.
So, this is the Cloud MD.
So, now, one second.
Now, so, I'm going to create things using Flask, because that's my favorite tool.
Some people prefer Node.js.
I mean, Node.js is a standard for web development.
But I always like Flask, because I always like Python.
Python just makes things very simple and very readable and so on.
So, let's do something here.
Okay.
So, the first prompt, we're going to create a minimal Flask app.
Let's say, create a minimal Flask app called Moneyclaw with a nice landing page.
You can see it here.
Okay.
I'm not sure if this is, okay, maybe I should zoom in.
With a nice landing page, it's about optimizing spending.
Use port 7010.
So, you can use any port above 5000, because when you run your app, it creates a port number.
So, that you can see the website based on that port.
And then use templates.
So, this is where I want to generate the HTML.
HTML.
As you can see, stuff like that requires some, like, small coding knowledge.
But that's okay.
Even if you don't have coding knowledge, just copy-pasting these kind of paths is enough, you know.
And then, a good thing is to add something, to add the word.
A good thing is to always add the word minimal code, so that it doesn't create some crazy amount of code.
And when you just write this and you have a generate code, most of the time, it gives you dark theme.
Personally, I always prefer a brighter theme.
So, you can say, make the theme bright.
So, the theme is like the colors of the website.
So, let's do it.
So, Issam, you wrote minimal code, but I'm assuming that in your cloud.md, you would have already
mentioned it, right?
So, is there a need for you to explicitly re-mention it?
Yeah.
Sometimes you have to mention things like three times or four times so that it's in its brain.
There's this thing called the lost in the middle, which means if you're, let's say, so you can
imagine this cloud descriptions here is going to be part of your prompt.
Right.
So, on top of this, all of this cloud.md would be appended to it.
Correct.
So, in the middle is like when your prompt is big, sometimes some instructions get lost.
Oh.
So, it's worth repeating the things that you want to emphasize, you know?
Okay.
Yeah.
So, let's create this.
I have a question.
Yeah.
Am I audible?
Okay.
So, if I didn't use the cloud extension, cloud code extension, and I actually use code,
does the file then can still be called cloud.md or it's just semantic?
So, I'm not hearing you well.
Maybe, are you close the microphone?
Yeah.
Okay.
I will, I'll type my questions.
So, you said like if you're using not cloud code, something else?
Yeah, she's going to type her question, she said.
Okay.
Yeah.
Are you using codex?
I never used codex personally, but I would say it's similar.
So, it should be similar.
You can just type the same.
I don't think it's called cloud.md.
I haven't explored it, but they must have something similar.
Okay.
There you go.
Thomas mentioned this.
You can use agents.md.
I think agents.md is more universal.
So, it works for all AI assistants.
Just to confirm, Ism, you're using cloud code desktop app, right?
Like not the cloud extension VS code.
No, no.
So, this is VS code.
So, here I installed VS code.
If you go to extensions and you do cloud code, you'll find it here.
You see here?
Okay.
This is the extension VS code.
This is the extension, yeah.
So, you install this and you get this thing.
So, when you open VS code, you have two things.
You have this chat.
So, this chat is not cloud code.
This is co-pilot.
This actually doesn't work very well.
This is the default.
Yeah.
You want to interact with this cloud code.
So, you see this icon here.
When you see this icon, you know that you're interacting with cloud code.
The reason why we use VS code is because it gives you a lot of visibility.
Like you can see all your files.
You can see a lot of different things.
You can see your terminal.
And you can see everything that's happening here.
So, it just gives you more.
It's like an integrated development environment, you know.
It's an IDE.
A nice IDE.
So, what's the difference between actually using Cursor and then using Sonnet or Opus models there
versus, you know, installing cloud code extension VS code?
Yeah, it's a good question.
So, Cursor is very similar, but Cursor doesn't have cloud code.
So, Cursor, you can use Sonnet and Opus.
That's true.
Yeah.
But, and also cloud code, if you see here, uses like Sonnet or Opus or Haiku.
But cloud code itself has, for me, what I noticed is that it has a much better harness.
So, it does the planning better, in my view.
It does execution of the commands better and so on.
Because it's more than just the LLM.
The Sonnet and Opus are just the LLM.
LLM, you have the harness, like the planning, keeping track of memory,
what to do next, executing commands.
So, cloud code, I found it to have a better harness.
Gotcha.
Yeah.
It's okay.
So, let's put this back in.
Let's run it.
Hopefully, it goes fast.
As you can see, I have 83% used.
But it will reset in three days.
I can't wait.
$700.
Really?
700?
Yeah.
Well, that's part of the company.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
So, you have cloud.md.
I'm running this.
As you can see, okay, it's doing a lot of different things.
You don't have to keep track of these things.
I usually don't read them.
I usually just drink coffee at this building.
But as you can see, it built this app.py.
So, I know some people don't have experience with code or haven't read much code before.
But part of this HACA course is to just have some experience with maybe reading a bit of the code.
But you don't have to understand what different statements are doing.
There you go.
App is running.
It created this app.py.
It created some files like HTML.
So, HTML is what is used to display your website.
And there you go.
So, we have this thing.
So, let's run this.
So, you see this play button.
When you click here, it actually runs it.
It's running already because I already had.
Okay.
There you go.
You see this thing?
HTTP 127.0.0.1.
So, this is what we call the local host.
So, you just copy paste this thing in your browser.
You can do a command and you click this.
And you get something.
You get something like this.
You see?
That was quick.
There you go.
Very nice, right?
Okay.
So, now what are we going to do?
We're going to build components.
We're going to build the components based on the thing.
Based on that Excalibur or that figure that we have built earlier.
So, remember this figure?
So, we're going to build those components.
Okay.
Let me see the prompt for this.
So, we're going to do multiple things.
So, this is the prompt.
It's always nice to add the navigation bar.
So, what is the navigation bar?
Let me.
Okay.
There's a way to add a browser here.
I think.
View.
Browser.
Yeah.
And then I'm going to put the URL here.
So, that we can see.
How it's updating.
So, this is our website, right?
So, the navigation bar is the thing at the top here.
So, in the navigation.
Okay.
In the navigation bar.
Let's remove these features, pricing and login.
Remove features, pricing and login.
And instead, add a tab.
Call components.
And clicking on it should take you to components.html.
It's like a website.
And there you have three subsections.
You have data connectors.
You have agents.
And you have tools.
As shown in the figure.
The figure is the one we showed in Xcaida.
Show them as cards similar to the ones in the dashboard.
Okay.
So, I'm going to move around a bit.
Let me also put this in the browser here.
View.
Browser.
Okay.
So, remember.
This is our Excalibur, right?
So, you can take a screenshot of this.
And then we can add this here.
So, once you create your figure, you can add it.
As you can see here, you can add it as an image here.
So, you want to show like what are your data connectors, your agent and tools.
But remember in the kickoff, we had this very nice components dashboard that I showed earlier.
You can also add that as a screenshot so that it can create that components dashboard.
Just bear with me and we'll run it.
Just bear with me, please.
I would like to have like another screen.
Okay.
So, remember this dashboard that we had before?
So, I will like share it in the, well, it's already shared in the hackathon website.
But you can also take the screenshot.
You can take the screenshot.
And then you put it here as well.
So, now we put two screenshots.
One for the flowchart and one for the, how we want the dashboard to look like.
So, we said, okay, show them as cards similar to the other dashboard screenshot.
Do not implement any of these components yet.
And for components that haven't been implemented, add a tag that says not implemented yet.
Okay.
Let's remove this.
Okay, let's go into the landing page.
It's adding a components.
There you go.
It's creating a components page.
Well, it's because it's still creating it.
You can, if you have any questions while it's building, feel free.
It's actually good that it takes a bit of time so that we all digest what's happening.
Right now, we're creating the components dashboard.
Because the idea here is that we have all these components
and we want to implement them one by one.
And once we implement them one by one, then we can create the workflows that we want.
So, here you are trying to create that new component on the nav bar.
However, this particular side that we are seeing right now, then what would this do?
Is it more like some place where you get the results
and component is where the real action is happening?
Yeah.
So, components is like where you have all these tools and data connectors.
Right.
Like here.
You see here?
Yeah.
So, you have Gmail, Google Calendar, Notion.
Okay.
The agent brain should only be AI agent.
Oh, yeah.
All these three.
Yeah.
We have the soul, the memory.
So, you see editable persona.
And then you have the tools.
Webster, sent to Telegram, generated dashboard, create report.
You see?
Does that make sense?
Mm-hmm.
So, now if I want to in the future update the data connectors, would it just implement on top
of it automatically?
Yeah.
So, once you have this, you can just say add a new data connector.
Okay.
Add a new data connector.
I don't know.
So, a new data connector could be Outlook, SharePoint.
Right.
What else is there?
Examples of data connectors.
A database.
It could be Supabase.
It could be Cloudflare, buckets where you save all your data.
All kinds of data connectors, right?
Anything where you can get data.
Oh, it could be KGG.
That's a data connector.
It could be Craigslist.
It could be your bank, credit card, statements, and so on.
Does that make sense?
Yeah.
Wherever you get the data from in order to make a certain decision for a certain thing.
Exactly.
Yes.
Right.
Whatever is the component of that particular decision-making in short.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Okay.
So, first things first, we're going to implement the Gmail components.
You're going to implement some of these components.
So, the first one is Gmail.
Okay.
Oh, no, no.
Actually, before the Gmail, I would recommend building this AI agent.
So, the AI agent that we can interact with.
It's different from Cloud Code.
This is the agent that lives in your app.
Okay.
I'm going to copy paste what I had.
Let me explain it.
So, now create the agent similar to the screenshot here.
And we're going to add the screenshot soon.
I'm going to also give it a path.
It's always nice when you build something.
It's always nice to tell Cloud Code or Codex, for that matter,
to give it exactly where you should implement it.
That way, it doesn't create like many, many different files.
So, I just want to implement the agent, this SRC.
So, the folder SRC is very common in coding.
SRCLMs.
It will do it by itself.
And two very good libraries is OpenRouter, which allows you to connect to different models.
and LANGraph.
And another thing that's very good is to say, add any libraries needed in requirements.
Because for your Python programming language, to use, let's say, OpenRouter LANGraph,
it has to install some libraries.
It has to install OpenRouter and it has to install LANGraph.
So, you can put it in what we call requirements.txt, so that it's automatically installed.
And we're going to give it some features.
Allow me to chat with the agent.
And here's another thing that's very cool.
I would very recommend this.
As you're creating components, like accessing Gmail or accessing OpenRouter,
there's some steps that you have to follow to get the API keys.
In order to know what are the steps, you can tell Cloud Code to add to the README.
So, the README is this README file.
So, it's empty right now.
To add to the README and how to acquire the API key.
And it will give you the steps, like which website to go to, how to register and so on.
I always like to make things into bullet points so that it's not overwhelming.
And at the end, clicking on the AI agent card.
Remember, we had this AI agent card.
So, when I click this AI agent card, it should take me to that interface similar to the screenshot.
I'll show you the screenshot shortly.
One second, there's a chat message.
Which model are you using now?
I'm using Sonnet right now.
I could use Haiku, but I think with Haiku, you might need a few iterations.
But Sonnet is a safe choice.
Opus is more expensive.
I think it's double the price.
But it can be used to be way more ambitious.
You can even maybe tell Opus, create a whole personal assistant that does all these things.
But I think Opus is good for like one shot different things instead of like having an iterative process.
I always recommend iterative process, like building from the ground up.
Because that way, you yourself are not overwhelmed.
And the AI agent is not overwhelmed in the sense that you do not get confused in how to extend and so on.
Yeah, so Molan, so use Opus if you have a very highly ambitious goal.
Like say, create a personal assistant for finances.
That's it.
And it does it for you.
How would we change the model it's using?
So you see here, there's this button here.
You can click it.
And then you can switch model here, you see.
And you can also specify the effort and how much thinking is required.
Okay, so let me show the screenshot.
I will share the screenshots in the website as well.
Okay, so this is a chatbot I built a while ago.
So I'm going to take the screenshot.
And then I'm going to paste it here.
Okay, let's hope it works.
Let's hope it works.
Enter.
So I, what exactly is line graph doing within this agent?
That was our question in the zoom.
So line graph allows you to have a, so a line graph makes it easy to build a harness.
So it makes it easy to let us, so remember we said we had LLMs and we had everything around it.
The things around it could be memory, the solve, could be long-term memory, short-term memory,
could be cron jobs, could be planning, could be executing different commands.
So line graph helps with doing these things quickly and efficiently.
So it doesn't have to implement everything from scratch.
Line graph is like one of the state of the art for building the harness around the LLMs.
So it makes things agentic very efficiently.
All right.
So now it's creating the.
So when you say that codex doesn't have a better harness than Claude, what do you mean?
What does it not have then?
Uh, no.
So codex also has its own harness.
Cloud code has its own harness, but based on what Powell said, they're comparable.
Right.
So maybe they have like similar ways of like planning, executing, breaking down the task
and so on.
As you can see here, you see how it breaks down the task?
Reading this, edit this, write this.
So this planning is involved.
Okay.
So that's the harness.
You can see visually basically.
Yeah, you can see.
Well, yeah, you can see visually, but it's also implemented at the back end.
Okay.
Like breaking down the task and doing things one by one.
Like all these thinking, no update, write this, write that.
So that requires a harness to do all of this.
Because what's the difference between a harness and just an LLM?
Is this an LLM?
Is this question answering?
Like you ask the LLM a question and it gives you back an answer.
The harness is like, how do you break things down?
How do you start things in memory?
How do you follow up?
So that's the harness.
Okay.
So it seems like it created the agent.
So we have, let's refresh this.
There you go.
You see here, Monte Claw, you have this agent.
You can choose different agents.
Let's do a GPT-4 or mini because it's cheaper.
Let's see if it works.
All right.
Hopefully it works.
Maybe if when it's like in VS code, it doesn't do it so well.
Just one second.
Do you need to set any key for this?
Oh yeah, you need.
So I'll show you that in a second.
First, I want to just check if this works.
So components, AI agent, let's say hi.
Okay, so I'm using this one.
Oh, I know why it's not working because we don't have the key.
Yeah, exactly.
That's right.
Yeah, you're right.
So let's go to the readme.
You see here?
There you go.
Getting an open router API key.
Go to open router and sign up.
Navigate to keys.
It gives you all the steps.
Create this.
Set it as this.
Open router supports some free tier models.
No credit card needed to start.
So you go to here.
I think it can just add.
Okay, let me just delete everything else.
Let's do the browser.
Let's do another browser.
So this is the open router.
It's like an API key.
So I have the key.
I'm just going to copy paste it.
Let me add another browser.
New integrated browser.
And just one second.
I'm just, I know I'm looking at all this code here.
I'm just going to put the code here.
Okay.
I'm just going to, so how do you paste the key?
You see the readme?
It says set it as open router API key.
So you go to this dot end.
This is, so dot end is where you keep all your keys.
And they're all secret.
And then I need to put the API key here.
So I'm going to put the API key here.
I'm going to like make this smaller.
So that you don't see the whole key.
So you don't steal all my money.
But I have it here.
Open router API key.
So I'll paste it here.
There you go.
So this is my key here.
So now hopefully, and now I think it should work.
And when you put an API key,
sometimes you have to rerun your program.
So I'm going to rerun it.
And then there you go.
Let's see.
Come on, don't fail me.
There you go.
You see, it responded.
Let's add.
Yeah.
Okay.
So now it responded.
Let me think what I should do next.
Yeah.
Okay.
So now it's like a.
What is the best way to spend money in one day?
It's just a random question.
So that takes time because it's like it's thinking and stuff.
Okay, here's something here.
You see, like it gives you this.
So it's not rendered properly, but you can tell your cloud code to render this nicely
and add emojis and stuff.
You can even say to add it to give it a personality.
You know, does this make sense so far?
Yeah.
Okay, good.
So now let's go to open claw.
Okay.
So can you please go back?
Yeah.
What is that total 45 in 285 out on?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Because I also said how many tokens.
So I can keep track of my spendings because you spend money per token.
Yeah.
So these are 45 tokens, I think.
And then you have 287 outside.
Based on how many tokens you sent and how many tokens you get back.
You can even say to give you an estimated amount of money every time you call it.
You can even have it report here, like the amount of money that you have spent.
So you can add all of those things.
Okay.
Yeah.
So there's a question.
Are you going to configure specific states for every use case and flow?
Well, not in this case.
But you're, yeah, you're welcome to like based, like you're on this agent and based on how it performs,
you can have an analysis of your agent of where are the bottlenecks and so on.
And then you can optimize them.
So you can do all of those things.
But it's always best to start with something minimal that doesn't have a lot of
bells and whistles, as they say.
And then based on your needs, you can add stuff.
It's always good to start simple and then add layers after that.
Okay.
Now that we have this agent next, let's do that Gmail.
So AI agent, we, I also added the stack of whether it has an LLM or not.
It's always nice to know which components have LLM and which components do not.
Okay.
So now let's do the Gmail.
So for the Gmail component.
Okay.
Let me paste this.
Now create a component.
So it's also good to give where the components should live.
That way you can keep things modular.
So I'm going to create a folder here.
Let's call it components.
So every component will have a single file under this folder components.
Okay.
So now create a component.
Let's call it accessgmail.py.
Similar to the screenshot that allows me to access my Gmail account.
I will share the screenshot shortly.
And then in the readme, show me how to create an API that connects with Google,
including in how to get the credentials from Google and the API key.
Show all the steps and the URL to get that API.
You know, creating API key for Google is actually not that simple.
It's not that complicated, but it's very convoluted.
It's very confusing.
So having it in the readme will make it very easy.
So now let me add a screenshot.
For this, just one second.
I have a lot of tabs.
So that's why I'm like, I'm just removing some tabs here.
Okay.
Just, just bear with me.
I'm going to add a nice screenshot here.
All these prompts that I'm showing here, I'm going to add them online in the website.
And maybe I should add more instructions.
So I'm going to add this thing here.
When clicking on the card, like the Gmail card, show a similar view as the screenshot that I showed.
Okay.
Should only load the page.
But where did you define that?
There are two parts to it, right?
One is the access of the Gmail itself.
And then using that information to show us over here.
So in terms of the access itself, are you giving it instruction on what emails to go after?
So in this case, for example, they're all expenditure related.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
Sorry.
What was the question?
So my question is that, are you defining it anywhere that when you go and access Gmail,
you have to access these XYZ type of email only?
Yeah.
So, yeah.
So as you can see here.
For, for Gmail, right?
So, yeah.
So I'm saying, so I gave the dates.
Okay.
Like from this month to this month and from who.
I can add some keywords like interact and so on.
So for example, I want only the emails that has the word interact.
Right.
Got it.
Okay.
So now I'm going to add.
Yeah.
So in the Gmail component, have interact to be the default subject keyword box and only
display the first five emails because I don't want to like display a lot of emails.
And also I can add, I'm just adding more like filters, basically.
I'm just adding filters and only have the date from and end to be the first and end of January.
So I just want the emails from the person to the end of January.
Okay.
Let's, let's, let's run this.
All right.
So this is good.
This is very good.
So now it's creating this file called access Gmail.
You see.
So it's always nice to have like one file per component.
Just because it makes it very modular.
Now, today is 7:30.
The Luma event 7:30.
Yeah.
Okay.
It's creating all these things.
Time moves very fast.
Okay.
Accessing Gmail.
Hopefully it doesn't fast.
Come on.
I like doing live coding.
Like I know that I can just have this maybe pre-recorded or just show it quickly.
Like already done.
I'm like, I already done this like five hours ago.
But it's always nice to see how this works in live, like in real time, because that gives you an idea
of how to deal with like issues or how to see like what you expect and how the AI agent is building your code.
So that's why I like doing live coding.
And also we can like be more dynamic.
So if we want to make any changes and so on.
Okay.
So this is all the Google API.
You see here setting up Google API credentials.
All right.
So let's go to this money claw.
Reload components.
There's the components.
This is the Gmail.
There you go.
You see.
So this will not work because I don't have the API key.
So let's go to the readme.
It says setting up Google API credentials.
So the idea is to go.
Okay.
So let me do something here.
Let me do something fancy.
View browser.
So you're going to go to this console here.
Ah.
Okay.
I can do this.
Let me put it this here.
I want to show you.
Show it to you side by side.
We go to the readme.
So this is the readme.
So it says.
Let me.
Go to this console.
So this is the console.
And then create a new project.
So if you go here.
It says new project.
There's a lot of YouTube videos on how to do this.
But it can get very confusing.
So let's say.
My app.
Or Moneyclaw.
We're just going to follow here.
So now the project name Moneyclaw.
Create project.
And then it says here.
Go to API and services.
You see.
So API and services.
And then.
You go to this.
OAuth.
You see.
OAuth consent screen.
It's always very confusing.
Okay.
OAuth consent screen.
Maybe settings.
It feels like it's always different.
Okay.
Ah.
Clients.
Okay.
I already have one.
But the idea.
Okay.
And then you do.
Create client.
You see here.
Oh.
It's because it's doing test.
Okay.
Moneyclaw.
Then you do like.
You show your app information.
So let's say.
Moneyclaw.
And you just put your email.
Next.
So you specify external.
As defined here.
Next.
And Google likes to change things.
Every.
Every now and then.
So that's why it gets confusing.
I agree.
Continue.
Create.
Okay.
And then you do this.
Create OAuth.
Client.
There's a lot of YouTube videos.
Then you do this desktop app.
As it says here.
Desktop app.
Create this.
And this is your client secrets.
You can download this JSON.
So now I'm going to go to my.
I'm just going to copy paste it.
All right.
Let me shorten this.
You see here the dot end.
And then you're going to create.
Another key here.
And let me just copy paste it.
You see this.
Google credentials path.
So whatever you download there.
You just copy paste it here.
And that will give you access.
To all your Google stuff.
Yeah.
Farah.
So.
What about the login and password?
Like where is it getting the password.
For your Google from?
So.
You see this website here.
I'm already logged in.
You see as my Gmail.
So that API key already has information.
About my password.
And user.
And username.
Okay.
And next time.
When you change your password then.
It doesn't matter.
So that one already just accesses.
All your Google stuff.
That's.
So you see this credentials.
Because.
Right.
And it is already connected to your account.
So anyone who has this.
Can access everything in your Gmail.
That's why you should be very careful.
OK.
So this is the key.
It can access all your Gmail stuff.
So it doesn't matter if you're changing your password.
Whatever you're doing.
Exactly.
Yes.
OK.
Yeah.
Because that's the API key.
Which is defined here.
As you can see.
Got it.
OK.
Yeah.
There's a question from Helen.
Let's see.
Yeah.
You had previously gotten API keys from open router.
And Gmail.
So.
Some apps.
Some services.
It's very easy to get the API key.
Other services.
Like Gmail.
Is very difficult.
For some reason.
So.
Based on the service.
Some API keys are much easier to get.
So that's why.
We had to do a lot of steps.
For Gmail.
Just because.
I think the reason.
Why they make it very difficult.
Is because Gmail.
Can contain many sensitive data.
So they want to make sure.
That people are very.
Intentional about.
How they're going to use their API key.
Does that make sense, Helen?
Yeah.
So now you can also add some scopes.
So what is a scope.
That we can add.
Let's see.
Okay.
So my scopes is like.
Because now I have API key.
That's accessing my Gmail.
A scope is like.
Can it read.
Can it read my Gmail?
So the API key is.
My Google account.
So we can add a scope.
So can it access my Gmail?
Is it read only?
Is it write?
Is it.
Can it access my calendar?
Like all these things.
So one scope that we can add.
Which is including the readme.
Is this.
See this.
Google APIs read only.
So we add this.
So now.
The API key will allow me to read my Gmail.
Does that make sense?
So that means if you had wanted.
It to create an email.
It wouldn't be able to do so currently.
Based on the scope.
You.
Exactly.
I cannot create emails.
I cannot send emails.
Okay.
You cannot delete emails.
Which is very important.
So I really recommend.
Just sticking to like.
Read only for now.
Okay.
So I mean.
Do you have to explicitly mention.
About the delete part.
Which you said.
Just now.
So these are all the scopes.
That I have.
The write part.
Does not exist.
By default.
At all.
Okay.
Yeah.
It doesn't exist by default.
Okay.
So now we have this.
Google credentials.
Let's hope it works now.
Gmail.
Ah.
Okay.
Uh.
I think I know why.
Just for a second.
Because it's expecting.
This credentials.json.
I use the.
Google credentials.
From .in.
For accessing.
Because there's multiple ways.
And how to make it a link.
To your credentials.
One way is.
To create that json.
But ideally.
I recommend just.
Having it in .in.
And just make it access from here.
So it's going to be.
Uh.
Okay.
Let's do this thing.
Now Google credentials.
Is read from this.
Okay.
There you go.
Uh.
Let's hope it.
It works now.
It has read.
All this.
Subject.
Interact.
Only get five.
And.
There you go.
So now I can access my Gmail.
Does that make sense?
It's good.
So one thing I want to do.
Is that if I click on download.
I wanted to download these emails.
Into a file.
So.
Okay.
Oops.
So here.
I said.
We're clicking on download.
Saves them in data.
With headers only.
So headers.
I mean like.
Just the subject line.
Okay.
So now we're gonna run it.
So it's gonna.
Allow me to download it in.
As a file.
And under data.
So it's always nice.
To have a folder called data.
Where you save all your things.
So let me refresh this.
Okay.
So next is.
Let's access notion.
So.
Let's go to notion.
I'm gonna show it shortly.
So this is my notion.
Agent Watson.
My goals are.
It's a simple goal.
Like it could.
Ideally you have all your goals.
For the year.
And so on.
So my goals are.
Optimize my money.
For the year.
So this is my notion.
So I want my.
AI app.
To be able to access.
This notion.
So we're gonna create.
The notion component.
Sometimes I'm not reading.
Okay.
So now.
We're gonna do this thing.
Now create a component.
As SRC components.
Access notion.
That allows me.
To view my page.
And this.
So you see this link here.
Is basically the link.
Here above.
You see the URL here.
Is just here.
Okay.
And then.
Always add.
Whenever you build a component.
Say.
In the readme.
Show me how to obtain the API key.
For notion.
For that page.
And then one clicking.
I'm gonna do the same thing as before.
When clicking on the card.
Show a similar view as the screenshot.
I'll show the screenshot.
However, it should only show the page.
Okay.
There you go.
And then allow me to edit it.
So where's the screenshot?
Access notion.
Yeah.
Go ahead for it.
Issam.
So here you have.
You know explicitly.
Taken the URL of that agent Watson page.
However, what if there are multiple folders.
Inside of notion.
Which you want the agent to access.
Then are you creating one agent per link?
No, no.
So for here.
We're just.
We're just fixing it to one page.
But you can make it.
Access all your pages.
How would you do that?
Because you just.
Used a URL.
And the.
If there are multiple folders.
That means there are multiple URLs.
Right?
So you just paste all of them together.
Yeah.
The only reason I did this.
Because I have a lot of pages.
And there's like.
Private information.
Right, right, right.
But I could potentially just say.
Allow me to access all my files.
And then.
Okay.
One way you could do is like.
Allow me to access all my files.
And have a drop down.
Like a drop down in my component.
That allows me to.
Switch between the notion pages.
Okay.
So you can do that.
Yeah.
Okay.
So this is my.
Well, the other notion page.
I mean.
I'll take a screenshot of this.
But you know like.
The screenshot here is more about.
How to organize how it looks.
So.
It's not necessary to build the component.
It's just because.
This is how I want the component to look like.
But you don't.
Like when you build your own app.
You don't need this kind of screenshot.
So I'm going to put that screenshot here.
And then I'm going to press into.
Uh.
Did I talk about the readme?
Yeah.
The readme.
Show me how to obtain the API keys.
For that notion.
For that page.
We might be a bit over time.
If you guys are okay.
Well.
You know.
The session is recorded.
So.
Yeah.
I do it.
Yes.
Sorry.
Maybe I have missed something.
But.
What purpose notion.
Is going to be used for.
So.
You could imagine.
It could be.
So.
Here.
The goal.
Of.
Because this is.
A money claw.
So.
Money claw.
The idea is to optimize your spendings.
Right.
So.
You could imagine.
Let's say.
You have your yearly goals.
So.
One thing could be like.
I want to buy.
A house.
In five years.
I want to.
Travel.
Three times a year.
So.
You can put all your goals in notion.
That's when your AI agent.
Looks at your.
Spendings.
It can also look at your goals.
From notion.
You know what I mean?
Yes.
But at the same time.
We have a chat window.
With the help of which.
We also can.
Kind of communicate with agent.
So.
Is it.
Is it an additional.
Way to communicate with agent.
In this case.
Or is it.
A midterm memory.
Or.
How should we treat it?
Yeah.
So you could potentially.
Just copy pages.
And send it to the agent.
That's true.
But.
This is more like a long-term memory.
Like fixed.
So the things that are more static.
Or long-term.
You can have them in notion.
So that you don't have to rewrite.
Your goals.
Every time you talk to your agent.
Does that make sense?
Okay.
Thank you.
So it's like.
You have all your long-term goals.
Like everything about your life.
That.
All your values.
Your goals.
Your vision.
Yeah.
And basically.
One pile.
Yeah.
Because of that.
I have asked one question in the chat.
But as you have said before.
You are not checking the chat.
So I would.
May I kindly ask you.
To describe data flow.
Or data flows.
For these particular apps.
Or agents.
Use cases.
Or at least one use case.
Because right now.
I'm trying to understand.
What do we expect.
From this agent.
And how do we expect it to work.
And how do we expect it to.
Go through everything that we have.
Yeah.
So the idea is that.
Okay.
You have these things.
Right.
So you get all your transactions.
From your Gmail.
Maybe some meetings.
Related to finances.
But Notion.
Is like.
Has all your goals.
Also.
It could have.
Also the personality.
You see this.
Sol here.
Because it could also be part of.
Notion.
So you can say like.
Make sure.
That.
Make sure that.
All your answers.
Are.
In three bullet points.
For example.
So you can give it.
All the instructions.
That are static.
In your Notion page.
You can also use.
The Notion page.
To keep track.
Of your finances.
So you can tell the agent.
To update this page.
With.
All your like.
Summaries.
Like whenever you talk.
To the agent.
And say.
To give you a dashboard.
Or a summary.
You can have it.
Edit.
The Notion page.
So the Notion page.
Is like.
Something that's more static.
That's the idea.
Okay.
And in the case.
Of Land Graph.
We will not be able.
To dynamically.
Add different skills.
And so.
That is something.
That I am worrying about.
Because.
I would like to.
Have more dynamic system.
And more.
Autonomous system.
What would you suggest.
To.
To kind of.
To improve.
You can do that.
So when you have Land Graph.
You can.
You can add skills.
To Notion.
If you want.
But you can also.
Have the skills.
Locally.
So you can.
You can ask.
Land Graph.
To create skills.
Dynamically.
And use those skills.
To.
To run your workflows.
So you can do that.
Yeah.
You can do that.
Okay.
Yeah.
It's not.
It's out of the scope.
Of this.
Lecture.
But you can do that.
Okay.
I'll explore this possibility.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Of course.
Farah.
Yeah.
So regarding the same thing.
Issam.
Please correct me.
If I'm wrong here.
But to me.
Notion is.
Pretty much looking like.
As though that.
Guiding light.
Which is helping.
The agent.
Make those decisions.
Which align with my goals.
Yeah.
Is that what it is?
Exactly.
For this specific use case.
It could be anything.
For this specific.
Yeah.
It can be anything.
But in this specific use case.
For example.
If it is finance related.
I want to go on a holiday.
In say six months.
So that is my goal.
Which I've put in this.
Notion page.
And every single time.
The agent tries to make a decision.
It tries to always.
Keep in mind.
That she wants to go in six months.
So.
Exactly.
Yeah.
It takes the decisions accordingly.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Okay.
Good.
Yeah.
So it's like.
You can think of this as a vision board.
Yeah.
Like you're writing your vision board here.
And then the agent accesses that.
Sees your spendings and.
Gives you out.
Okay.
And then tries to do the direct.
Like go in.
Goes in that direction.
Exactly.
Yes.
Okay.
Thank you.
Yeah.
You're welcome.
Tanvi?
Basically on the same.
I just wanted to confirm.
Like it seems like Notion is just.
One of the note taking apps.
And can be replaced by whatever.
Source of.
You can use Google Docs.
If you wish.
Yeah.
You can use anything.
I just wanted to show like something outside Gmail.
Like I wanted to show today.
Like how to connect with different services.
Yeah.
As well.
I missed the Landgraf.
Part.
Are we going to use that here?
Like it.
You don't have to.
I just said Landgraf.
Because if you want to create something.
A complicated agent.
Yeah.
You can use.
I ideally use that Landgraf.
Like with skills and stuff.
But here.
for this Monique law.
I haven't.
Utilized Landgraf's capabilities.
But isn't Landgraf like.
N8N with basic.
I mean.
With basically nodes.
That can be.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Work together.
Yeah.
So this is.
So here.
Okay.
See here.
Landgraf.
Yeah.
It's like a graph.
With nodes.
And edge.
Nodes and edges.
So you see here.
Like add node.
Chat.
Add edge.
It's.
So it makes it easy to create.
Like an N8N workflow.
You're right.
Okay.
Sounds good.
Yeah.
It sounds good.
Can you hear me?
So remember like.
I think 10 minutes ago.
I said.
I'm going to skip this.
Yeah.
I was planning to create fake emails.
Like 100 fake emails.
Transfer.
Yeah.
To make it more fancy.
Uh.
But yeah.
So if you want to test your program.
Ideally you create like fake emails.
It's more than using your personal email.
Because to get this 5 or 10 emails.
They are tracking the whole mailbox.
I would say.
Right?
So are you okay about that?
Well.
The things I'm using right now.
Just to interact.
That's fine.
Okay.
Just focus on like.
Innocent things.
Uh.
But ideally you don't use like.
Your main personal email.
Yeah.
That's why I was wondering.
Ideally you use another email.
And uh.
Have different uh.
Items there.
You know.
Does that make sense?
Yeah.
Mate.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Okay.
So let's look at the readme.
And how to connect to Notion.
So getting a Notion API key.
So you go to this thing called.
My integrations.
Hopefully it's not hallucinating.
Oh.
There you go.
And then uh.
I think you can click on one of them.
Like this.
And this is the API key.
You see this.
This is the API key.
You just.
Copy.
You can.
If you show it.
You can copy it.
And uh.
You see here.
Add the dot on.
Dot in.
Add this API key here.
You see.
Okay.
I'm going to copy the API key.
Uh.
Flowcraft.
This looks quite different than.
Just bear with me one second please.
Uh.
Let's go.
All right.
So I'm going to copy this thing.
Oops.
Uh.
Okay.
Use this as the API key.
So let's see.
Uh.
Yeah.
Okay.
So it's going to take this Notion token.
I mean.
It doesn't matter the name.
Right?
As long as the API key is there.
So.
I don't image.
Just add the API key.
Okay.
Hopefully it works.
Notion.
Run.
There you go.
You see.
My goals are to optimize my money for the year.
I want to buy.
And then you can edit it.
Like I can say.
I want to travel to Spain.
I want to travel to Spain on December.
About two week vacation.
I saved it.
So let's see if this is also in the website.
There you go.
You see.
I want to travel to Spain.
So you see.
Like we just showed how to like edit.
And read at the same time.
So.
That's very cool.
Okay.
We have six minutes.
But I think I'm going to go up to 7:45.
For this.
So hopefully you could stay.
Because I want to show you like telegram as well.
Okay.
So what's next?
The next part.
As the telegram component.
So we want to access telegram.
Okay.
So telegram.
So we could use WhatsApp.
But WhatsApp.
As I said in the kickoff.
It's very hard to integrate.
The API key.
But telegram is very awesome.
In fact.
Like it's very popular.
You can access it.
And.
It's on your phone.
You can send messages.
And it sends messages back.
Okay.
So how do we.
Uh.
Do it.
So you have here.
You go back.
So we have this telegram component.
Send to telegram.
Not implemented yet.
Let's implement it.
I'm going to do the same thing.
For the telegram component.
When click.
When clicked.
So this one.
Go to a screen.
Submit to the screenshot.
Where I can send a message to my telegram.
Add to the readme.
And how to connect to the API of telegram.
I always like to.
Say minimal code.
Okay.
Let's add the screenshot.
I don't think that screenshot is really necessary.
But.
So this is like a telegram screenshot.
So let's copy paste this.
Or no.
Let me copy that.
There you go.
I'm going to paste it here.
All right.
Okay.
I didn't specify that I should create that access.
Telegram.
Ah.
You see.
This is a good thing.
So I have one chat.
So even though I didn't say create send telegram.
It's learned my workflow.
It learned that.
For every component.
I have a different file.
So it's learned that I can do this.
You know.
So that's very, very cool.
It's writing this in telegram.
Just to show you what telegram looks like.
So this is the telegram website.
So I have an agent called agent Watson.
Hello.
So these are like different things.
Okay.
It's writing all these things.
So I was chatting with it earlier.
As you can see.
All right.
All.
So another thing I've done in the readme.
In the cloud.md.
They say always end with saying all done amigo.
You see here.
That's why it always says all done amigo at the end.
Okay.
So let's look at the readme.
So setting up a telegram bot.
So the idea is to open telegram and search for bot father.
So you go to telegram.
One second.
There's a lot of screens.
So there's this thing called bot father.
It's available by default.
This is the bot father.
And then you say new bot.
Okay.
Let me read this.
You say new bot.
And then.
All right.
A new bot.
How are you going to call this?
You can call it something.
Let's call it money claw.
One, two, three, bot.
Now let's choose a username.
It has always ended with bot.
So that's the username.
There you go.
So this is my token.
And then that's it.
That's pretty much it.
So I'm just going to copy that token here.
Let's see.
I'm going to copy paste it.
Fast claw.
So you need two things.
Telegram bot token.
To get a telegram chat ID.
Okay.
So now.
Let's see if it works.
Just make sure to use.
Because I wanted to use those two things.
I think it already uses them.
Okay.
There you go.
So now let's refresh this.
Send to telegram.
Hola amigo.
So if it does this.
Let me just.
You can just take a screenshot.
And you put it here.
I'll click this.
Okay.
That was like a small issue.
So whenever you have failures.
Just put it back into cloud code.
And say fix this.
So now I think it's going to fix it.
Just allow.
All right.
So let's reload this.
I think I need to refresh.
Just one second.
These failures.
These failures are always expected.
There you go.
If it happens again.
I can like.
Hola amigo.
Okay.
Let me just put this.
Put this error.
Put it here.
Fix this.
So sometimes if there's like a bad error.
You can like switch from.
Sonnet to office.
Okay.
There's some 32 bit stuff.
All right.
Let's see how funny it works now.
Oh wow.
Let me run it again.
Sorry about this.
Okay.
Refresh this.
Let me just run it again.
And while this is running.
I will run something else at the same time.
Because I want to do the dashboard.
So sometimes you have this endless loop.
Like it has an error.
And then it just keeps going.
Any questions while this is running?
Okay.
What if there is an action.
That needs to be performed.
On a regular basis.
For example.
In this case.
You know.
I saw some transactions.
With Murilo.
Right.
So if you want to.
Make this agent.
Do this one task.
That moment.
It reaches.
Over 500.
Send me a message.
Right.
Which means.
It needs to.
You know.
Continuously access.
Those emails.
In order to find.
Those interact.
Related emails.
And then send you the.
You mean like.
Like a heartbeat.
So every like.
Few minutes.
It checks.
Yes.
Oh.
Why is this error happening?
There you go.
Oh.
You see here.
I'll show you in a second.
See here.
So let's put a message.
I think because.
There was no message type.
So let's say.
Money claw.
Law is the best.
Law for optimizing money.
Send.
There you go.
You see.
And then.
It's all.
I just got notification.
In my phone.
Showing that.
So you said like a heartbeat.
Like every five seconds.
Or something.
Right.
Yeah.
Like a regular check-in.
To see that you are on track.
And you're not overspending.
Right.
So like the moment.
Basically the point is for.
Us as users.
Or clients.
To not.
Be tracking this manually.
Yeah.
So I'm going to show you.
How to do it.
Like an example.
A heartbeat.
Okay.
Let me just.
Go here.
Okay.
So you have.
This guy.
Right.
I just sent this whole.
So let me add.
Something else.
About like a.
Like a heartbeat.
Oops.
Sorry about that.
So.
You see this.
I have this run command here.
Let me add this prompt.
In the telegram component.
Under the run.
Button.
Add.
Ascent.
Every x seconds.
Where user can select.
X.
That sends the message to the user.
Every.
X seconds.
So it will be.
What do we call.
Like listening mode.
Or like.
In running mode.
And it will be just doing that.
All the time.
So.
Let me.
Show you that.
In a second.
Okay.
So let's refresh this.
So every five seconds.
I wanted to send.
Don't spend any money.
There you go.
You see.
Every five seconds.
Does that answer your question.
Yeah.
Because like.
You just like.
Run it.
And it's in running mode.
And then you don't have to look at it.
You just have it in the server.
And it's just running.
Running.
So that's pretty much it.
Yeah.
Don't spend any money.
So this is how you do it.
Like the heartbeat.
It's like a cron job.
All right.
So now.
Remember.
Like we have downloaded.
Some messages here.
So let's.
Create like an artifact.
Like a dashboard.
Showing all these different money stuff.
So we're going to create.
The dashboard component.
So remember.
We had.
Let me put it on.
Like side by side.
Like this.
And then.
Yeah.
Generate dashboard.
Not implemented.
So I want like to.
Have an interactive dashboard.
That I get like.
The messages from Gmail.
And then it.
Shows them.
Okay.
Let's see here.
I'm going to copy paste this thing.
Okay.
For the dashboard component.
Create an interface.
Similar to the other components.
But in the.
In the.
In the input box.
A lot.
User to select between.
All these Gmail files.
So because I have this Gmail here.
I wanted to select.
Like anything that I have here.
This gets downloaded.
I want it to be.
Selected.
And then add a run button that.
Okay.
Let me just break this down.
To make it easier to read.
Should show a bar chart.
On the right hand side.
Showing the payments.
From different users.
Allow the user.
To select between.
Bar chart.
And pie chart.
So these are all like.
My interests.
Make it visually appealing.
With hovering.
That shows more info.
And then I say.
It should be in this.
Access dashboard.
And clicking on.
Generate dashboard component.
Should get you to that interface.
Parse the messages properly.
To know from.
Each.
It was received.
And transferred.
Because you see.
Like it says.
You've received.
You've transferred.
And so.
I want to be able.
To break it down.
And that's it.
So this will be a dashboard.
That like.
Looks at all the messages.
Let me add.
A fake files as well.
Okay.
One second.
So I have these.
Fake files here.
I called it.
Gmail messages.
So all these are fake.
You see here.
Like all these transfers.
I want to like.
Have all these.
Be able to be transferred.
Okay.
Access dashboard.
Is coming.
What do we have next?
Okay.
Let's go up to 8 p.m.
Sorry about that.
But there's a lot.
Of learning to do here.
Huh?
A lot.
Of learning.
Okay.
It's accessing the dashboard.
Because I also want to show you.
The web search.
There's a very nice.
API that you could use.
For web search.
Like it's adding the rows.
Updating app.
Like Pi.
And.
In the.
After this.
Like by tomorrow morning.
I will show.
Like all these steps.
In a much more structured format.
So you don't get lost.
Okay.
So it says.
I think it's.
In built.
Okay.
Generate dashboard.
Let's run this.
Okay.
You see here.
This is my brother.
By the way.
Mohamed.
Laraji.
Celia.
I can do.
Pi chart as well.
You see here.
Let me do the other one.
But maybe it cannot.
Parse it properly.
Okay.
Allow it to.
Also.
Be able.
To parse.
So you can.
Even specify.
The file.
So.
This one here.
Because it's not.
Parsing this properly.
Okay.
It's like.
Identifying.
So that way.
Like it can.
Deal with different.
File formats.
So I'm just.
Allowing it to.
Be able to parse.
Different.
File formats.
There's a lot of information.
Here today.
All right.
Let's refresh this.
So this one works.
Let's see this one.
There you go.
You see.
Okay.
It doesn't look very well.
Oh wow.
Okay.
It looks nice.
You see.
So the bar chart.
Oh there you go.
Very cool.
Total receive.
Total spent.
Interactions.
Okay.
So the next component.
So let's do web search.
Let's say you want to find.
Alternatives to Netflix.
And so on.
I mean.
Of course.
You can do Google search.
But you need to be able.
To connect it to the agent.
That's why we're creating.
These components.
So let's create.
The web search component.
Okay.
So now.
Create a component.
Called.
This search.
That uses the brave.
API key.
Similar view as the Gmail.
So we're not going to add.
A screenshot.
Allow the user.
To specify the query.
And only display.
The first five results.
And then read me.
Show how to obtain.
That API key.
You're going to.
Use this thing called.
The brave API key.
It's a very.
A nice.
Service.
To allow you to access.
The web.
Programmetically.
So we're going to add.
This brave API key.
I'm going to go to.
Ask.
Law here.
Okay.
Let me add the key.
Because I have the key here.
I was going to add it itself.
Pontificating.
Any questions.
While this is running.
Or comments.
Or is everyone tired.
I'm not sure.
If you already answered.
But there is a question.
From Thomas.
Okay.
Hi.
So I'm wondering.
About front end.
Interface.
Is this like.
Open cloud.
Is this something.
We interact with the via.
I mean.
So.
You see this interface.
Here Thomas.
This is more.
Like admin control.
You know.
This is more.
Admin control.
It's not like.
It's not the interface.
That's going to be used.
By people really.
It's admin control.
So you have.
All these components.
You have workflows.
And you enable them.
And then you access.
These services.
Through.
Let's say.
Your telegram.
Through your notion.
Anywhere you want.
So.
This web app.
Here is less.
About.
What the user access.
Is just admin.
Just to enable.
Or disable.
Different components.
Does that make sense.
Thomas.
Yeah.
Of course.
You can have.
Another interface.
So.
What we're building.
Now.
Is just the.
Admin dashboard.
To see.
All the components.
The workflows.
And then you can have.
A separate interface.
For the end user.
For people.
Who are using your app.
Which could be.
Completely different.
It's always good to have.
A dashboard.
Like.
An interface.
For the end user.
And a dashboard.
For the admin.
Where you can control.
All the components.
And stuff.
And the reason.
Why we're building.
Components.
One by one.
As you can see.
It's much easier.
That way.
And you can test them.
And also.
It gives you.
A very nice overview.
Of like.
What's going on.
And so on.
The user front end.
Or like.
On here.
But he.
That's very easy.
Like.
That's.
Not today.
I mean.
We have something.
Yeah.
That sounds good.
I'm just trying to imagine.
For example.
If.
If I want to see.
My own breakdown.
For.
You know.
Like.
The different.
Spendings across.
And I want to do that.
Via telegram.
So.
So I'm just trying to imagine.
The use case.
To target.
So would that be like.
Is it.
Won't that be.
Easier for me.
To open this dashboard.
And access it through it.
My web.
Rather than actually typing in my telegram.
Can you give me.
For example.
A pie chart of you know my spendings.
Of this thing across this time period.
Yeah.
So you can do that.
You can have like a nice end user interface.
Where you just specify.
Like the Google account.
Like you just.
You just put the.
Which.
What kind of spendings you're looking for.
Like some input parameters.
Yeah.
And then what kind of dashboard.
And they just displays it.
It's a very simple end user.
A dashboard.
So you can do that.
As an end user.
Does that make sense?
And even like through telegram.
Yeah.
For both.
Okay.
So you can have it.
Also connect with telegram.
Which we will show it shortly.
Okay.
Sounds good.
How you connect with telegram.
And then send it.
And then send it to you.
Okay.
So let's go to components.
Web search.
Okay.
Let's hope it works.
I want a cheaper.
Alternatives.
Netflix.
I mean this is not like very smart.
It's just a dumb.
Okay.
It doesn't have API key.
I think because I need to rerun it.
Let's rerun this.
Here we run this.
Okay.
Refresh.
Netflix.
Okay.
Let me.
Just give me one second.
And they can just say fix this.
So after this.
Okay.
We have like around 14 minutes for the 8:00 PM.
And now like really, really over time.
But we're going to show two workflows.
On how to chat with your telegram as an agent.
And also to give you a summary of your spendings.
Okay.
So this is going to be rerun.
Let's rerun this.
There you go.
You see here.
Or like maybe better here.
So web search.
There you go.
You see that.
It's like a Google search for your agent.
And then if you go to the read me.
You see here.
It tells you exactly what you need to do.
Getting a brave search API key.
Go to this website.
Go to the API dashboard.
Get the data.
And add it to you.
That's pretty much it.
And I think you have like.
1,000 searches per month or something.
Or per day.
I don't know.
But something like that.
Of course there's free tier.
And so on.
Any questions so far?
Okay.
So next.
We're going to do two workflows.
One workflow for interacting with your telegram.
So when you interact with telegram.
And then it sends the message.
And then you get back from your agent.
And then the other workflow is accessing your Gmail.
Getting the data.
And then showing you a summary on telegram as well.
Okay.
Let's do the telegram one.
To do the workflows.
We're going to create another.
So now we only have this components tab.
And the AI agent.
Let's add another tab.
Which is very important.
Which will be about workflows.
And the workflows will be a combination of tabs.
So now create workflows.
Let's make it put this here.
So now we're going to create workflows.
Add a workflows tab in the nav bar.
That shows.
Implemented in workflows under SRC workflows.
I'm going to create.
So we have components.
And we're going to create workflows here.
Show two workflow cards.
And which components they use.
So best practice is like.
For every workflow.
You specify exactly.
Which components it's going to use.
First workflow card.
Is chat with an AI.
Chat with AI on telegram.
That uses the AI agent component.
And the telegram component.
Second workflow card.
Is summarize interact spendings.
From Gmail to telegram.
This should use the components.
Gmail, AI agent.
And telegram.
Minimal code.
Enter.
So now they are real stuff.
Create these components.
And now we're going to create the workflows.
That combines these components.
And now it's a lot of things.
Squash in one.
Next time.
If I run this hackathon again.
It will be like a two hour and a half.
Meanwhile.
Can you just scroll up the readme.
To see the Gmail set up again.
Yeah.
It's this one.
See.
Oh thank you.
Yeah.
I'm going to take a screen short.
If you tell like your AI.
I'd also have to set up.
Google API credentials.
It will give you all these things.
As I did.
Like the prompts that I showed.
There's nothing.
Okay.
So now.
I have workflows now.
So I go to workflows.
I have these two.
Chat with AI on telegram.
And I have this thing.
So let's implement them.
It shows you which components.
AI agent in telegram.
Gmail.
So let's do the first workflow.
All right.
Now implement the chat with AI on telegram.
As SRC.
Same thing.
One file per workflow.
Workflows.
Chat with AI on telegram.
The interface should be similar to the telegram component.
But allow me to select the model.
When user clicks run.
It will be listening to receive messages.
So it will be listening mode.
And a message.
And a message is received.
Display the message.
Okay.
And when a message is received.
Display the message.
And then use the AI.
To respond to the message.
And send it to telegram.
Respond by one message at a time.
There you go.
Okay.
So now it's creating.
Chat with AI.
You see.
Very cool.
Very structured.
All of these procedures.
I came up with it myself.
By the way.
It's much better than how a lot of other people do it.
It's just very cluttered.
And overwhelming.
I know this is a bit overwhelming.
But trust me.
Like doing it another way.
Is way more overwhelming.
I mean.
We did a lot.
In like one hour.
15 minutes.
So far.
Just creating the app.
So let's look at this.
You see here.
It's getting the.
From the components.
It's getting this send message.
And so it's getting.
With these two components.
The LLM itself.
Build agent.
And the send telegram.
All right.
Let's see.
So I'm going to have my telegram here.
Refresh.
Go here.
Let's do something easier.
Run.
So now it's listening.
Let's see.
So it's in listening mode.
Hi.
Oops.
Can you help me.
With my math homework.
I don't know why it's not running.
One second.
Let's fix this.
There's always issues.
Always happens.
I think it's because there's another process.
I think it's because we had this other thing.
That was running as well.
Okay.
Killing the old process.
So let's try now.
Let's do GPT-L4 mini.
Let's open telegram.
Okay.
Integration.
And differentiation.
Oh, it's stuck.
I mean, ideally it should work.
Oh, there you go.
You see?
But it's huge.
Okay.
It's running something.
You see?
I think it's repeating.
I think there's a.
Yeah.
But it's running.
You see the concept, right?
Like it's easy to fix.
Like you can say like respond by one message at a time or something.
But it's an easy fix.
Does that make sense?
So now it's like through telegram.
I'm able to communicate to my AI agent and it's a response to me at the same time.
Just because of time, it can be easily fixed.
But you see how it's done.
Okay.
The last workflow.
The last workflow would be
summarizing the thing.
Summarize interact spending.
So now implement the workflow for summarize interact spending as this.
Basically, first loads the first 10 interact messages for the month of February from the Gmail
that takes the subject line.
Allow the user to modify the month and the number of messages that repeat to that agent.
Send it as a summary.
Allow the user to also enter the system prompt.
Add a button that says listen to summary.
So this is important.
Add a button under run that says listen to summary, which makes the agent in listening mode.
If the user sends the word summary on telegram, it should do the whole workflow.
Anything else?
Say I don't know what you mean by that.
Make sure the agent sends only one message.
Okay, now it's creating this summarize.
So it's using the components fetch emails from the Gmail.
Send message and then get updates.
All right, let's see.
Okay, almost done guys.
Okay, I just like a show of hands.
Does this whole thing make sense?
I'm just going to paste it on
Zoom chat and put a thumbs up if you're if you're this.
And put this dead the skull if you're like completely lost.
Yeah, it takes a lot of things going on at the same time.
But the main point of this lecture is just to show you like the main process.
As you can see, every component, every workflow is like similar process, right?
It's like, okay, you have all these components.
We did this flow chart at the beginning.
We got this dashboard.
And then for every component, you click and then you create it.
Okay, let's hope this works.
Let's go to workflows.
Summarize this.
Okay, I even gave it to your personal advisor.
This is the personality.
10 messages.
Okay, let's run this.
And let's see our telegram.
There you go.
You see, interact summary.
You have all these things.
There you go.
You can make it, you can make it.
So it's doing markdown, but you can ask it to display it much better with emojis and stuff.
One thing you could do, you can make it listen, listen to summary.
So let's say you're in your phone.
And you want it such that whenever you send the word summary on your phone to telegram,
it gives you the summary.
So you do this thing called listen to summary.
So it's listening.
So it's running on your server.
It's always listening.
Like it's waiting for your message.
So let's put something other than summary.
Let's put hello.
It should say, I don't know what you mean by that.
You see?
Because that's what we said.
We said like, if you say anything that's not summary, you say this.
Now let's put summary.
It should do the other thing.
It keeps looping it and doing it again and again.
But yeah, that is pretty much it.
So now we have this telegram web connected with these workflows.
And these components.
I just have a last question, right?
Yeah.
Just because right now you are running this in a local host.
And if you turn off your laptop, it's done.
So doing to deploy this somewhere and even.
Yeah.
Render.com.
Oh, render.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
That's right.
I mean, I would show.
We'll show this like later on through the week.
But once you have things running on your local host, deploy it and render.
So you deploy it and render.
And then you allow it.
It's connected to your telegram and so on, you know?
Okay.
Got it.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Because it needs like a way to serve the model.
It needs to be hosted somewhere, you know?
Of course, no one else.
So in order to.
So let's say you deploy it and render.
In order to protect it from other people to use it,
you can add like a login screen or you cannot access unless you have some kind of a key.
You know what I mean?
Yes, sure.
Yeah, that's it.
So we just built a whole kind of, I would say this is like 70% of the personal assistant
because I could integrate with Google Calendar.
It could add memory to keep track of what you're doing, create a report and so on.
But we have all these components, right?
Our web search and then we have these.
Two workflows.
Of course, you can add a lot of workflows.
You can have all them running, you know?
Cool.
So we reached the end.
It's like half an hour more than what we had agreed on in the lecture.
So thanks a lot for staying.
Any questions or last comments?
Great session.
Thanks, Isem.
Yeah, of course.
I know there's a lot of things, but maybe next time I should break it down into two lectures.
But at the end of the day, you just follow it and then it's going to work well.
Yeah.
Thanks for summarizing all of this, Isem.
I know it must have taken a lot of time for you to prep for all of this.
And it really helps.
Thank you for the work.
Thank you.
I appreciate that.
Yeah, it was a good exercise.
Awesome.
Well, thanks everyone.
You have a good one day.
And I'm going to release the next module for this tomorrow.
Looking forward to your apps.
Thank you.
Thank you, Isem.